Guide to the Livingston Farrand papers, 1921-1939.
Farrand, Livingston Papers
- BOK-BON Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Bok, Edward W.; Boldt, George C.; Bonn, Morritz J. National Committee Against Prepayment of the Bonus.
- BOO Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Boochever, Louis C. Dept. of Public Information.
- BOO-BOR Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Boochever, Louis C.; Boomer, L. M.; Boothroyd, Samuel L.; Gherardi, Bancroft. Dept. of Public Information.
- BOR-BOS Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Born, Max; Boring, Edwin G.
- Boston Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  Richtmyer, F. K.; Ellery, Edward. New England Health Institute; Sigma Xi Society.
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1923 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Office of the Comptroller.
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1922-23 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1924-25 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Bostwick, Charles D. Office of the Comptroller., 1925 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1925-26 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1926-27 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1927-28 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1927-28 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1928-29 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1928 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1930-31 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1929-30 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1931-32 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1933-34 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1935-36 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1936 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Bostwick, Charles D., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Bosworth, Francke H., 1925-37 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  White, J. DuPratt. College of Architecture; University Plan Commission.
- Bosworth, Francke H., 1921-25 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  College of Architecture.
- Bosworth, Francke H., 1926-30 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  White, Andrew Dickson. College of Architecture.
- BOT-BOW Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- BOW-BOY Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Boyle, James E.
- BOY-Boys Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Boyle, James E.; Boynton, Frank David. Boys' Clubs of America.
- Boys Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Kirkland, J. B. Boys' Clubs of America; Boys' Farm and Training School.
- Boys Miscellaneous., 1929-37 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  West, James E.; Harrison, Ralph A. Boy Scouts of America.
- Boys-BOZ Miscellaneous., 1923-30 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Boy Scouts of America.
- BRAG-BRAD Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Bradford, Eugene F. Office of the Registrar and Director of Admissions.
- Bradford, Eugene F., 1931-35 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Office of the Registrar and Director of Admissions.
- Bradford, Eugene F., 1030-31 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- BRAD Miscellaneous., 1928-36 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- BRAD Miscellaneous., 1927-35 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Bradley, H. Hunt.
- BRAD-BRAK Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Bradley, J. Chester.
- BRAM-BRAZ Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Brauner, Olaf M.
- BRE-BREN Miscellaneous., 1922-29 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Breasted, James H.; Breed, Robert S.; Brehmer, William G. H.; Brent, Charles H.
- BREN-BRET Miscellaneous., 1926-36 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Bretz, J. P. Bishop Brent Fund.
- BRET-BRIG Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Bretz, J. P.; Brewster, George W. W.; Bricker, Garland A.
- BRIG-BRIT Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Brindesi, Olympic; Bristol, George P. British-American Club.
- BROA-BROO Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- BROO-BROW Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Broughton, L. N.; Emanuel, Victor; Brown, Charles R. Brooks-Bryce Foundation; Corson Browning Prize.
- BROW Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Brown, Charles R.; Brown, Elmer E.
- BROW Miscellaneous., 1924-33 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- BROW Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Browne, Arthur W.
- BROW Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Browne, Arthur W. Brown University.
- BRU-BU Miscellaneous., 1921-32 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Bruere, Henry; Bruno, Alexandre; Rose, Flora; Buck, J. Lossing (Mrs. ), ie. Pearl S. Buck.
- BUG-BUD Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Buck, Pearl S. Board of Trustees - Budget Committee.
- Buffalo Miscellaneous., 1921-26 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Buffalo Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Buffalo Miscellaneous., 1927-35 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- BUF-BUN Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Bull, Harry G. National Committee for Mental Hygiene.
- BUN-BUR Miscellaneous., 1920-33 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Pan American Union; Dept. of Interior Bureau of Mines.
- Burdick, Charles K., 1922-32 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Pound, Cuthbert W. Committee on Military Training; Law School.
- Burdick, Charles K., 1925-29 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Taylor, Myron C. Law School.
- Burdick, Charles K., 1923-26 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Thompson, George J. Law School.
- Burdick, Charles K., 1932-34 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Ladd, Carl E. Law School.
- Burdick, Charles K., 1929-32 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Hausman, Max. Law School.
- Burdick, Charles K., 1929 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Law School.
- Burdick, Charles K., 1928-29 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  Law School; Messenger Lectures.
- Burdick, Charles K., 1926-28 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Burdick, Charles K., 1935-37 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Burdick, Charles K., 1934-35 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- BURF-BURN Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Burnett, Clough Turrill; Burnett, Archie C.
- BURN-BURR Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Burr, George Lincoln; Sabine, George H.; Evans, Austin P.
- BURR-BURT Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Burritt, Maurice C.; Burton, Ernest D.; Burton, M. L. University of Chicago; University of Michigan.
- BURTT-BUT Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Burtt, E. A.; Butler, Nicholas Murray.
- BUT-BYZ Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Hoy, David F.; Byrd, Richard E. Butler University.
- Burtt, E. A., 1931-34 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Butterworth, J. E., 1929-33 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Graduate School of Education.
- Butterworth, J. E., 1926-37 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Butterworth, J. E., 1935-36 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- CA Miscellaneous - Calendar., 1922-37 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Cadman, S. Parkes; Calder, W. M.
- Calendar - CAL Miscellaneous., 1922-29 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Eastman, George. Committee on Calendar; National Committee on Calendar Simplification.
- CAL-CALI Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Cornell Club of California; University of California; California Council on Oriental Relations.
- CALK-CAM Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Calve, Emma; Campbell, George Carver.
- CAM-CAP Miscellaneous., 1920-32 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Boyle, James E. Canadian Cooperative Wheat Producers; Canton Christian College.
- CAP Miscellaneous., 1925-37 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Caplan, Harry; Wilson, Lewis A.; Captanian, Grant. University of Cape Town; American School of Classical Studies at Athens.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1930-37 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Keppel, Frederick P.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1929-35 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Keppel, Frederick P.; Lester, Robert M.
- Carnegie Corporation., 1922-29 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching., 1927-29 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Savage, Howard J.
- Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching., 1926-27 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- CAR Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Carleton, William P.; Carnegie, Andrew.
- CAR Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Carpenter, Walter S.; Carver, Walter B. Child Labor Amendment.
- CAR-GAS Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Carver, Walter B.; Cassady, Maynard. Cornell United Religious Work.
- CAS Miscellaneous., 1925-32 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Cassell, Gustav; Castle, William A.; Caster, Kenneth E.
- CAT Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Catlin, George E. G.
- CAT Miscellaneous., 1923-29 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- CATT-CAY Miscellaneous., 1921-35 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  Cattell, J. McKeen; Cavalier, J. Caucasian Society of America; Cayuga Press; Cayuga Lake.
- CE-CEN Miscellaneous. Century Association., 1923-37 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Century Association., 1920-27 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- CH-CHAM Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Chamard, Henri; Chamberlain, Austen.
- CHAM Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Chamot, E. M.
- CHAM-CHAO Miscellaneous., 1921-29 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Sage Chapel., 1931-37 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  Memorial Chapel.
- Sage Chapel., 1933-35 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Sage Chapel., 1931-33 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Sage Chapel., 1929-30 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Sage Chapel., 1927-29 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Sage Chapel., 1925-36 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- CHAP-CHAS Miscellaneous., 1924-36 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Chapman, J. Frank.
- CHAS-CHEL Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  Chase, Harry Woodburn; Chelmsford, Lord. University of North Carolina; Chautauqua Institution.
- CHEM Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Curtis, Harry A. American Institute of Chemical Engineers; Chemical Foundation; Dept. of Chemistry.
- CHEM-CHEV Miscellaneous., 1917-36 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Cherrington, Ernest H. Carnegie Corporation; Chemical Laboratory Building (Baker Laboratory).
- Chicago Miscellaneous., 1931-37 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Cornell Club of Chicago.
- Chicago Miscellaneous., 1926-30 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Vail, Roger S.; Bernays, Edward L. University of Chicago.
- Chicago Miscellaneous., 1926-28 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Taylor, Myron C.; Daily, Orville G.; Payne, Oliver H.
- Chicago Miscellaneous., 1922-26 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- CLAS-CLE Miscellaneous., 1921-37 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Clausen, Bernard C. Cornell Class Reunions; Cleanliness Institute; Cleveland Community Fund.
- CLE Miscellaneous., 1921-33 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Van Blarcom, Conant. Cleveland, Ohio.
- CLI-CO Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Cody, Henry John. Coeducation.
- COF-COK Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Kendall, Hayward; Coffin, Henry Sloan; Coffman, L. D.
- COK-COL Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Colcord, Samuel; Coleman, George L.; Cutten, George B. Cornell University Orchestra; Colgate University.
- COL Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  Colman, Margaret. College Entrance Examination Board.
- COL-COLU Miscellaneous., 1923-32 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Callahan, Henry White; Peyton, Ruth. University of Colorado; African-American students; Columbia University.
- COLU Miscellaneous., 1922-29 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  Butler, Nicholas Murray. Columbia University.
- Coffin, Foster M., 1924-26 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  Alumni matters.
- Coffin, Foster M., 1923-24 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Coffin, Foster M., 1921-22 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Coffin, Foster M., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Coffin, Foster M., 1931-32 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Coffin, Foster M., 1926-29 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Coffin, Foster M., 1929-31 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Coffin, Foster M., 1934-37 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- COM Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  Comstock, John Henry; Comstock, Anna Botsford; Landman, Isaac; Weaver, Paul J. American Hebrew; Commencement.
- COM Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Gannett, Frank E.; Stutz, Harry G. Commencement; Committee on Commencement; Commission on the Coordination of Efforts for Peace; Board of Trustees - Committee on General Administration.
- Commission on the Coordination of Efforts for Peace., 1931-33 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  Wilkins, Ernest H.
- COM Miscellaneous., 1925-34 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Wilkins, Ernest H. Commission on the Coordination of Efforts for Peace; Commonwealth Fund.
- COM Miscellaneous., 1928-36 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Communism; Comstock Publishing Company.
- Commencement., 1933-36 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Commonwealth Fund., 1926-31 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Farrand, Max; Shimer, Alma E.
- Commonwealth Fund., 1926-32 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Farrand, Max.
- Comstock Publishing Company., 1931-34 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Gage, Simon H.
- CON Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Conant, James Bryant. Conference of British and American Professors of English; Conference Committees.
- CON Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  MacDonald, Alexander. Conference of Universities; New York University; Congress of American Industry; New York State Conservation Dept.
- CON-COO Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  New York State Conservation Dept.; New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets.
- COO Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Cooke, Carlton P.
- Cooke, Walter P., 1925-31 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- COO Miscellaneous., 1922-30 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Cooke, Walter P.; Coolidge, Calvin; Lunt, Alfred E.
- COO-COP Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Cooper, Hugh L.; Cooper, Lane; Cope, Joshua A.
- COP-COR Miscellaneous., 1923-29 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Cope, Joshua A.; Copeland, Ernest; Greene, Howard.
- Cornell Research Foundation - Ezra Cornell Inn., 1929-34 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Treman, Robert E.; Peer, Sherman. Beta Lactose.
- Cornell Law School - Cornell Miscellaneous., 1924-34 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  Cornell, Katharine; Cornell, Mary Emily; Caplan, Harry; Cooper, Lane. Cornell Law Association; Cornell Society of Engineers.
- Cornell Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  Donlon, Mary H.; Mann, Albert R. Cornell Society of Engineers; Cornell United Religious Work; Cornell University Athletic Association; Cornell University Chest.
- Cornell Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  Upson, Maxwell M.; Newman, Jared T.; Mann, Albert R.; Wood, Franklin S.; West, James E.; Whitney, Jessamine S. Cornell University Christian Association; Barnes Hall; Widow; Cornell, Wisconsin; Women on the Cornell University Board of Trustees; Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs.
- Cornell Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Hart, Dennis C.; Donlon, Mary H.; Requardt, Gustav J.; Cornell, Charles Ezra; Cornell, Franklin C. Cornell College; Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs; Cornell Alumni Corporation.
- Cornell Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Cornell, Charles Ezra; Cornell, Katherine Bouck; Cornell, Clara; Cornell, Franklin C.; Cornell, Mary Emily. Cornell Alumni News; Cornell Club of New York.
- Cornell- In-China., 1921-35 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Moran, Hugh A.; Hambleton, Roscoe L. University of Nanking; China Union Universities; China.
- Cornell Miscellaneous., 1921-37 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Becker, Neal Dow; Langdon, Jervis; Cornell, Ezra. Cornell College; Cornell Club of New York; Cosmopolitan Club.
- Cornell Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Cornell, Ezra; White, E. B.; Bishop, Morris G.; Antell, Bertel W.; Flack, Harold; Schoellkopf, Paul A. Cornell Independent Association; Cornellian Council.
- Cornellian Council. Palmer, Archie M., 1934-37 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- CORN Miscellaneous. Cornwall, George A.; Cornwell, Ralph T. K. Corning Glass Works; Dept. of Religion (Proposed)., 1922-33 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- COR-COST Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  Corollo, S. C.; Corson, Hiram; Otis, Amy. Cosmos Club.
- Costs of Medical Care., 1932-33 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Committee on the Costs of Medical Care.
- Costs of Medical Care., 1929-32 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- COT-COU Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  Cottrell, Casper L.; Metzger, Jeremiah. Council on Foreign Relations.
- COY-COY Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  Cousins, John Copping; Coville, Luzerne. Council for Moderation; Council of Church Boards of Education; Council on Foreign Relations; Courier-Journal of Louisville; Cayuga Preventorium.
- CRAB-CRANE Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  Crampton, C. Ward; Crane, Henry H.; Crane, Charles B. National Shakespeare Federation.
- CRANE-CRAW Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Graver, Bradford N.; Crawford, Ivan C.; Crawford, Mary M. Caruso American Memorial Foundation.
- CRAW-CREW Miscellaneous., 1922-32 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  Creighton, James E.
- CRI-CRO Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  Crowell, James W.
- CRO-CUNN Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  Crowell, James W. Crusaders, Inc.; Cornell Club of Cuba.
- CUM-CURR Miscellaneous. Farrand, Margaret; Curie, Marie; Curran, Henry H., 1923-34 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Curtis, Charles E., 1924-31 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- CURT Miscellaneous., 1923-35 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Curtis, Charles E.; Curtis, C. W.; Olds, Fred A.; Emmett, Daniel D. Sage Chapel; North Carolina Historical Commission; Dixie.
- CURT Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Curtis, Otis F.; Curtis, Ralph W.; Cushman, Robert E. Arboretum.
- CURT-CUT Miscellaneous., 1921-34 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Cutler, Paul C.; Cutten, George B.
- Cushman, Robert E., 1930-32 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Schurman, Jacob Gould. Messenger Lectures.
- Cushman, Robert E., 1926-31 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Schiff Lecture Committee.
- DAB-DAL Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Myers, William I.; Dale, George Irving.
- DA-DAW Miscellaneous., 1923-33 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  Dallenbach, K. M.; White, J. DuPratt; Taylor, Myron C.; Daly, Victor R.; Damrosch, Walter; Dapping, William 0.
- DAR-DAY Miscellaneous. Vernon, A. W. Dartmouth College., 1923-34 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- DAV-Davis Miscellaneous., 1930-37 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Davenport, H. J.; Adler, Alfred; Davis, Charles; Bentley, Madison.
- Davis Miscellaneous., 1922-31 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Davis, Charles; Davis, E. Gorton.
- Davis - Day Miscellaneous., 1924-37 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- DEA-DEF Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Dean, Arthur H.; Dean, Daniel; Dechert, D. 0.
- DEF-DEL Miscellaneous. de Forest, Henry P.; Delano, William Adams., 1924-35 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- DEL Miscellaneous., 1922-27 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  Delano, William Adams. Willard Straight Hall.
- University of Delaware., 1923-27 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Kirkbride, Raymond W.
- DEL Miscellaneous., 1925-30 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Delta Chi Alumni Foundation. Bogert, George Gleason. College of Law., 1921-23 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- DELT - Dennis Miscellaneous., 1921-36 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Dennis, L. M., 1922-23 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  Dept. of Chemistry.
- Dennis, L. M., 1922 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  Brown, Charles O.; Parsons, Charles L. Dept. of Chemistry; Americanism.
- Dennis, L. M., 1922-23 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Dennis, L. M., 1927-29 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Dennis, L. H., 1926-27 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Dennis, L. M., 1923-26 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Dennis, L. N., 1921-23 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Dennis, L. M., 1930-34 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Dennis, L. M., 1924-31 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- DENO-DET Miscellaneous. Derham, Milo G. Denver, Colorado., 1921-30 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- DET-DEV Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  Lynah, James; Place, Harrington; DeVane, William Clyde. Dept. of English.
- DEV-DEY Miscellaneous., 1927-34 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  DeVane, William Clyde.
- DI-DIE Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  Diederichs, Herman. Cornell University Athletic Association; College of Engineering.
- Diederichs, Herman., 1922-30 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  College of Engineering.
- Diedrichs, Herman., 1934-37 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- DI-DJ Miscellaneous., 1921-31 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Diederichs, Herman. College of Engineering; Child Labor Amendment.
- DO-DON Miscellaneous., 1928-37 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Doak, William; Donodore, Dorothy Anne; Dodds, Harold W.; Dodge, Amy; Doherty, William J.; Walter, Thomas U.
- DOM-DOW Miscellaneous., 1923-37 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Donlon, Mary H.; Douglas, Walter. Dormitories.
- DOW-DREY Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Downing, Augustus S.; Dreyfus, Louis Alexander.
- DRI-DRU Miscellaneous., 1925-36 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Drummond, Alexander M. Military drill; Drill Hall (Barton Hall); Drinking.
- Drummond, Alexander M., 1926-35 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- DRU Miscellaneous. Drummond, Alexander M. Drury College; Dept. of Public Speaking., 1921-28 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- DUB-DUN Miscellaneous., 1923-36 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  Dublin, Louis I.
- DU-DUP Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  Duniway, Clyde A. du Pont de Nemours & Company.
- DU Miscellaneous., 1922-23 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  Kimball, Dexter S. du Pont de Nemours & Company.
- DUQ-DUR Miscellaneous., 1927-34 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Gage, Simon Henry; Durham, Charles L.; Durham, Davis C.
- DUR Miscellaneous., 1922-29 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Durham, Charles L. Cornell University Christian Association; Howard University.
- DURY-DY Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  Dusser de Barenne, J. G.; Macrae, John; Dyce, Elbert James. Honey patent; Dwight Scholarship.
- EA Miscellaneous., 1922-37 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Eagleson, Wilson Vashon; Shephard, James E.; Cadman, S. Parkes; Eames, Arthur J.; Witherspoon, Laetitia H.; Diederichs, Herman; Eastman, Edward R.; Eastman, Emma S.; Eastman, Elaine Goodale. Committee on Earlier Closing; American Agriculturist Research Foundation.
- EA Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Ghosh, S. P.; Eastman, Edward R.; Eastman, George. National Committee on Calendar Simplification; Eastman Kodak Company.
- EC-ED Miscellaneous., 1923-34 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  Gannett, Taylor W.; Eddington, Arthur Stanley. Economic Security Act; Committee on Economic Security.
- ED-EDS Miscellaneous., 1922-36 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  Eddington, Arthur Stanley; Daniels, John; Edgerly, John P.; Edgerton, Henry W. English-Speaking Union of the United States.
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1926-31 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  Horner, Harlan H. University of the State of New York.
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1925-31 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  Skinner, Avery W.; Sullivan, James L.; Horner, Harlan H.
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1923-28 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  Skinner, Avery W.; Cole, Ernest E.; Downing, Augustus S.; Blauvelt, George A.
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1922-23 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  Downing, Augustus S.; Graves, Frank P.
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1924-33 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  McCormack, Alice C.
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1921-29 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1929-30 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- United States Office of Education., 1929-31 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- United States Office of Education., 1924-29 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- United States Office of Education., 1932-34 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- United States Office of Education., 1922-29 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- United States Office of Education., 1921-32 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1932-33 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  Horner, Harlan H.
- New York State Dept. of Education., 1933-37 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Education. Colcord, Samuel; Battle, George Gordon; Curtis, Emerson. Dept. of Education; University Faculty; Sentinels of the Republic; Committee on Educational Publicity in the Interests of World Peace., 1922-32 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Edwards, Richard H., 1926-27 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  National Council of Religion in Higher Education; Cornell University Christian Association; United Christian Work at Cornell.
- Edwards, Richard H., 1924-27 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Edwards, Richard H., 1921-25 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Fosdick, Harry Emerson; Sze, Sao-ke Alfred. National Council of Religion in Higher Education; Cornell University Christian Association; United Christian Work at Cornell.
- Edwards, Richard H., 1934-37 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Cornell United Religious Work.
- Edwards, Richard H., 1932-34 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Edwards, Richard H. Cornell United Religious Work., 1930-33 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Edwards, Richard H., 1927-29 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Edwards, Richard H., 1927-28 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- ED-EG Miscellaneous., 1927-37 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  F. Edwards, Boyd; Egmont, Westy. Graduate School of Education; College of Engineering.
- EG-ELI Miscellaneous., 1922-34 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  Egmont, Westy; Eidlitz, Robert J.; Einstein, Albert; Eliot, Samuel A. International Law Research Institute.
- ELK-ELM Miscellaneous., 1922-33 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  Elmer, Herbert Charles.
- ELM Miscellaneous., 1922-35 (Box 10, Folder 10)